{
    "id": "f2c21a61fa674a5fa1751d84d689cb39",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The poor people ................................... to the will of the tyrant.",
            "description": "Bent is the past tense of bend.",
            "answers": [
                "bent",
                "bended",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They ........................................ him hard until he fell unconscious.",
            "description": "Hit is the past tense of hit. ",
            "answers": [
                "hit",
                "hitted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Civil war has .................................... the nation.",
            "description": "Torn is the past participle of tear.",
            "answers": [
                "tore",
                "teared",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The puppy ...................................... a hole in the stockings.",
            "description": "Tore is the past tense of tear.",
            "answers": [
                "tore",
                "torn",
                "teared"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ........................................ his money in his shoe.",
            "description": "Hid is the past tense of hide.",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hided",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They are searching for ...................................... treasures.",
            "description": "The past participle form of hide is hidden. Here it is used as an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "hid",
                "hided",
                "hidden"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly the bomb ....................................",
            "description": "Burst is the past and past participle of burst.",
            "answers": [
                "burst",
                "bursted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... my hand while cooking.",
            "description": "Burn can be regular or irregular and the forms burned and burnt are both correct.",
            "answers": [
                "burned",
                "burnt",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A mosquito just ....................................... me.",
            "description": "Bit is the past tense of bite.",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "bited",
                "bit",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The hikers .......................................... their way up the hill.",
            "description": "Wound is the past tense of wind.",
            "answers": [
                "winded",
                "wound",
                "wounded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ....................................... a diamond necklace to the party.",
            "description": "Wore is the past tense of wear.",
            "answers": [
                "weared",
                "wore",
                "worn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His failure ........................................ his parents.",
            "description": "Upset is the past tense of upset.",
            "answers": [
                "upset",
                "upsetted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}